{
    "id": "f0f915613fa44c548259777af8324156",
    "title": "Conjunctions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He passed the test ....................................... he had a good teacher.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "hence",
                "because"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I eat neither meat ......................................... fish.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "or",
                "nor"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She is poor ............................................ happy.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "and",
                "as",
                "but"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I can .......................................... sing nor dance.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "either",
                "neither"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I was tired ............................................. I went on working.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "and",
                "but",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Both Jane .......................................... Alice are introverts and get along very well.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "and",
                "as well as",
                "as well"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "......................................... the car was badly damaged in the accident, it needs to be repaired.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "For",
                "Since",
                "Hence"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We felt bored ............................................ went to the movies to relieve our boredom.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "and",
                "because",
                "that"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Rahul must give in and apologize ................................................. Praveen will not forgive him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "without",
                "unless",
                "or else"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The children were playing hide and seek and James was hiding in the garden ........................................... the rain started pouring down.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "when",
                "while"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}